nightzookeeper.com 2016-05-11

# Night Zoo Teacher • Privacy Policy

**Privacy, Data, Cookies and Marketing Communications**

Last Updated: 13 September 2015

**Introduction**

We would like to take this opportunity to welcome students, teachers, parents and guardians to the world of the Night Zookeeper. The Night Zookeeper is a fantastic place for children to learn, play and interact safely online. The Night Zookeeper is accessible at our website,www.nightzookeeper.com (the “Website”) and our mobile applications. The Website and all its content and related sites are the property of Wonky Star Limited (registered under company number 07706300 and the registered office of which is 19 New Rd, Brighton, East Sussex, BN1 1UF (the “Company”).

The Company is committed to complying with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). This is a US law which controls the use of information collected directly relating to children under the age of 13. 

In this policy we will:  
explain what we will do with the information you give us;  
tell you how we collect personal information and what we do with it; and  
how we aim to make the Website a safe environment for children to use.

**Registration**

**Applications**

**Night Zookeeper Story Pairs User**

If you have downloaded the Night Zookeeper Story Pairs mobile application we collect no information about you personally. There is a link in the application to  the Website the terms of use for which are below.

For your animal to be selected to be featured in the Night Zookeeper Story Pairs mobile application you will need to register with Night Zookeeper, create an animal and agree to our terms and conditions.

If you have any feature suggestions or would like to talk to the developers of Night Zookeeper Story Pairs please get in touch.

**Drawing Torch User**

If you download the Night Zookeeper Drawing Torch mobile application we collect no information about you personally. However we do use Google Analytics to record anonymous statistics about how the application is used. This includes: which tools are used and which missions are most popular. These analytics are collected for the sole purpose of improving our mobile application. There is a link on the Drawing Torch mobile application that directs to [](http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.drawingtorch.com&t=ZTNhNWQ2OGMxOWU0MDgxMjhkMmE4YTNjOWQ1MzQ1ZGNlMWFlMThkZSxUbU4zdWpESg%3D%3D)[http://www.drawingtorch.com](http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.drawingtorch.com&t=ZTNhNWQ2OGMxOWU0MDgxMjhkMmE4YTNjOWQ1MzQ1ZGNlMWFlMThkZSxUbU4zdWpESg%3D%3D).

**Teleporting Torch User**

If you register on [http://dashboard.nightzookeeper.com](http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fdashboard.nightzookeeper.com&t=ZWUzMjYzYmVkOGUyNzI5ZjMyYzJmNTI3MTdjMjQ2YTI4OWRiZmJjOSxUbU4zdWpESg%3D%3D) or on the Teleporting Torch app then you must provide a valid email address and by doing this you confirm that you are over 18 years of age and accept our terms of use as well as those of the iTunes store.

As we mentioned, the registration process on the app and Website requires an email address. Our intention is to collect parent or teacher email addresses, which we can use for the purpose of marketing communication and important updates regarding Night Zookeeper. We do not share any collected email addresses with any 3rd party and we include unsubscribe links on all correspondence so that users can have their email addresses deleted from our database if they wish. The company has a data protection policy to ensure the safety of your information.

**As a parent or teacher, you then have complete control over the information we collect from our users. We suggest you create nicknames for your little Zookeeper’s to keep them completely anonymous and also select their age. You can edit this information at any time and delete their accounts via the online dashboard.**

All content created using Night Zookeeper Teleporting Torch is used in keeping with the policy described for NightZookeeper.com. See below for full information.

As a parent or teacher you also have complete control over who views your children’s artwork and stories. All work is private by default. However you simply have to hit the ‘Share Artwork’ button and then you will be able to post the content on Facebook, Twitter or anywhere online. In doing this you accept the terms of use of these websites. You can, if you wish, choose to make the artwork private again therefore stopping visitors being able to view the content via the link.

Please keep in mind that anything, once shared online, can be ‘screen grabbed’ by others.

**Marketing Communications  **

On our website we provide forms where users are invited to submit their email address. The intention is to collect parent and teacher email addresses, which we can use for the purpose of marketing communication. We will not sell or trade personal information to other companies. We also do not share any collected email address with any 3rd party and we include unsubscribe links on all correspondence so that users can have their email addresses deleted from our database if they wish. The company has a data protection policy to ensure the safety of your information. 

**NightZookeeper.com  **

**Cookies**

Cookies are files stored on a user’s computers for the purpose of keeping records. Cookies are used on the Website. 

We use cookies to analyse, collect and store anonymous statistical data about visits to the Website.

We may also collect information about your computer, mobile phone (or other portable or static device used to access our site) and your visit to the Website, including where available your IP address, operating system, session_id, login, screen name and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our partners.

We may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file and/or similar tools which are stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive to report back anonymous data to us. They help us to improve the Website and to deliver a better and more personalised service.

Generally, cookies may be used to enable us to:

estimate our audience size and usage pattern.

store information about your preferences, and so allow us to customise the Website according to your individual interests and provide a more personalised experience to you.

recognise you when you return to the Website  (for example, we store your sound settings from the last time you visited the Website).

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. 

By continuing to use the Website and services you give your pre-informed consent to us using cookies (and other similar tools) on your visit. If you subsequently wish to revoke this consent, you may do so by deleting the cookies (and similar tools) via your browser tools settings. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of the Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system may issue cookies when you log on to the Website.

If you want to switch off cookies you can opt-out of them by disabling cookies on your computer. 

**Information We May Collect**

We know how important your privacy is to you, and it’s important to us that you and children feel safe and secure on the Website. We want to make sure that you have the very best experience of The Night Zookeeper and so we may sometimes ask you for certain information and you may send personal data to us (such as your name, school name, email address and contact details) when you subscribe, sign up, or purchase products from the Website, to allow us to do that.

We may also record which parts of the Website you are interested in as well as user traffic patterns and Website use. Most of the time we’ll use this data anonymously. This information will be kept securely in accordance with an internal security policy. In some cases the data you provide may be used to:

process your User Content, your subscription to the Website and to enable your use of the Website;

open and run your account and provide you with an up to date, efficient and reliable service;

generally run the Website;

if we sell or transfer our business.

By subscribing and submitting your data you agree to this use.

We will only use information collected about you in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. We will not resell or use your data in any ways other than those that you have given us permission for. We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.

If you believe we have information about you that you do not want us to have or that is incorrect please contact us as described below and we will correct or remove the data as you request, as soon as reasonably practicable.

**Sharing Of Information**

Where we are required to share information with third parties we will always ask your permission or in the case of a child user, their parent or guardian’s permission. We may share personal information where we need to:  
act against any fraud or illegal activity we consider to be taking place via the Website;  
protect the well-being and human rights of other users on our website;  
assist in any investigations, court orders or unlawful activity;  
protect our rights and comply with legal proceedings; and  
merge with another company. We will notify you before we share your information in this instance.

We actively encourage children using the Website to:  
not share any personal identifiable information on the Website;  
not identify themselves other than by using their username or Night Zoo animal’s name; and  
not post anything on their profile which discloses their personal identity such as age, address, school name etc.

**Website Security**

The only way that you will be contacted for personal identifiable information will be through an official email from the Company. If you receive a request for personal information from persons claiming to be the Company please report this directly to roa[…](http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com%2Frecaptcha%2Fmailhide%2Fd%3Fk%3D01nya-p7iw8cb-doqp3xdyra%3D%3D%26c%3D91gj750vtvew1y6yz9ypkfjgdy5lxf0rwcbyjzajcv4%3D&t=ZTdiMjUwYzdmOTMxYjllNDVkMTU1MzVlNWIyYjI5ZTg1ZDZiYTI3NixUbU4zdWpESg%3D%3D)@nightzookeeper.com

**Links To Other Websites**

We may provide links to other websites from time to time. However, we do not sponsor or endorse these websites and you should check their Privacy Policies fully before using their websites. Please ensure that you also refrain from using any personal information on various other websites that you may visit.

**Changes To This Policy**

This policy is being constantly reviewed and updated in order to remain in line with current UK law. Please re-visit this page to check for any updates and changes that may have occurred.

**Questions**

If you have any questions please contact us at roa[…](http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com%2Frecaptcha%2Fmailhide%2Fd%3Fk%3D01nya-p7iw8cb-doqp3xdyra%3D%3D%26c%3D91gj750vtvew1y6yz9ypkfjgdy5lxf0rwcbyjzajcv4%3D&t=ZTdiMjUwYzdmOTMxYjllNDVkMTU1MzVlNWIyYjI5ZTg1ZDZiYTI3NixUbU4zdWpESg%3D%3D)@nightzookeeper.com or send us a letter to Customer Service, Wonky Star Limited, Hodgson & Dawes, 19 New Rd, Brighton, East Sussex, BN1 1UF

That’s it for the legal stuff! Thanks for reading.
